{
    "subject": "resource/Madame_Butterfly_(1915_film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "resource/Silent_film",
    "human_readable": "The language of the 1915 film Madame Butterfly is Silent film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8432648181915283,
            "question": "What type of film is Madame Butterfly (1915)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4581766724586487,
            "question": "How is the dialogue conveyed in Madame Butterfly (1915)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4499967396259308,
            "question": "In what year was the film Madame Butterfly released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44164490699768066,
            "question": "Name another famous silent film."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39431971311569214,
            "question": "What is the significance of silent films in cinematic history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35952967405319214,
            "question": "What filmmaking era does Madame Butterfly belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28395140171051025,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of silent films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24783611297607422,
            "question": "What musical accompaniment was often used with silent films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2308391034603119,
            "question": "Was Madame Butterfly a talking picture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22427377104759216,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a famous actor from the silent film era?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the 1915 film Madame Butterfly is Silent film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6912_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Madame Butterfly a talking picture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6912_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical accompaniment was often used with silent films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6912_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of silent films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6912_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6912_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it mentions that \"This, of course, is the silent film version of David Belasco's Madame Butterfly...\" and also mentions that the film was a \"silent film directed by Sidney Olcott\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the 1915 film \"Madame Butterfly,\" which indicates it is a silent film, supporting the statement that the language of this film was silent."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}